Contact

7722032011 (Home) rahaanareynolds30@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rahaanasmith-703a9786 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Treatment
Vital Signs
Medical/Surgical

Rahaana Smith

Competent, Professional, and Caring Nurse. Fort Pierce

Summary

Hello,

I am a bachelor's prepared Registered nurse. I'm competent and caring nurse with four years of solid experience. My expertise in nursing consist of Med-Surge and PCU-Telemetry. I previously worked for Lawnwood medical center and Heart Institute, which is a level two trauma center. Currently, I am a registered nurse for Traditions medical center. My main goal for each shift is to provide safe, competent, and compassionate care to high acute patients. To continue my growth, and provide the highest quality of patient care, I plan to obtain a FNP/ARNP degree. If you are an employer looking for a registered nurse to join your team please contact! My email address includes: rahaanareynolds30@gmail.com. My professional resume is provided down below.

Experience

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions
Registered Nurse
March 2011 - Present (9 years 6 months)
Port Saint Lucie, Florida

Parallon

Travel Registered Nurse March 2017 - June 2017 (4 months)

Bradenton, Florida

Under the general supervision of the Director/Manager, renders professional nursing care in accordance with physician's treatment plans and standards of evidence based practice/care. In doing so, assesses patient's condition, plans patient care, administers prescribed drugs, provides treatments, provides appropriate patient education, and evaluates patient's progress, records pertinent observations and report responses to drugs and treatments. Assists with examinations and prepares instruments and equipment. Advocates for patient in order to achieve the best possible

Lawnwood Medical Center Register Nurse March 2014 - March 2017 (3 years 1 month) Fort Pierce, Florida Area

Progressive care nursing jobs involve care for patients requiring close monitoring and frequent assessment, but who aren't unstable enough to need ICU care. PCU nurses monitor cardiac and other critical vital signs and detect any changes, thereby enabling intervention of life-threatening or emergency situations. Many PCU patients receive complex medications that may require titration based on the patients vital signs The PCU nurse is sometimes also called a step-down nurse and the PCU is also known as cardiac stepdown, medical stepdown, neuro stepdown, surgical stepdown and ER holding.

Education

Keiser University-Ft Lauderdale
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2013 - 2015)

Keiser University-Ft Lauderdale
Associate of science in nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2011 - 2013)